<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<COVID_VAX_AE>
<TEXT><![CDATA[A 73-years-old female patient received first dose of bnt162b2 (PFIZER-BIONTECH COVID-19 VACCINE; lot number and expiration date unspecified), via an unspecified route of administration on 28Jan2021 18:30 at single dose (right arm) for covid-19 immunization. Medical history included allergies, asthma and Clostridium difficile (c.dif). 

Patient had allergies to medications, food or other products. The patient was not pregnant. Concomitant medication included rosuvastatin within 2 weeks of vaccination. The patient received other vaccine within 4 weeks prior to Covid vaccine included 1 dose of pneumonia vaccine on 07Jan2021 at a clinic. 

On 28Jan2021 18:30, the patient experienced mild nausea. Treatment was not received for the event. Prior to vaccination, patient was not diagnosed with COVID-19 and since the vaccination, patient has not patient been tested for covid-19. Outcome of event was recovered on an unspecified date.  Information on the lot/batch number has been requested. She had no side effects except for the pain at the site of injection. She wanted to know if it needs to be monitored more. But the next day she said it's just mild and not big deal.
]]></TEXT>
<TAGS>
<AE spans="283~292" text="allergies" id="A0" certainty="positive" comment="NA"/>
<AE spans="294~300" text="asthma" id="A1" certainty="positive" comment="NA"/>
<AE spans="350~359" text="allergies" id="A2" certainty="positive" comment="NA"/>
<SVRT spans="688~692" text="mild" id="S0" severity="NA" comment="NA"/>
<AE spans="693~699" text="nausea" id="A3" certainty="positive" comment="NA"/>
<AE spans="1033~1037" text="pain" id="A4" certainty="positive" comment="NA"/>
<SVRT spans="1153~1157" text="mild" id="S1" severity="NA" comment="NA"/>
<LK_AE_SVRT id="L0" link_AEID="A4" link_AEText="pain" link_SVRTID="S1" link_SVRTText="mild" comment="NA"/>
<DATE spans="188~197" text="28Jan2021" id="D0" comment="NA"/>
<DATE spans="647~656" text="28Jan2021" id="D1" comment="NA"/>
</TAGS>
<META/>
</COVID_VAX_AE>